A Guide to the Tredegar Iron Works Records, 1801-1957
Library of Virginia
- Appendix A: Oversize Folders, Extent: 15 cu. ft. (7 boxes, 6 map case drawers, and 1 rolled tube). (Box Boxes 1227-1233, Folders 1-93)
  - Kilby Locomotive & Machine Works-Sketch of an angle bar-1906 (Folder f023)
  - Kinston Lumber Co.-Sketch of fish plates-1906 (Folder f023)
  - E.W. Heitmann Co.-Blueprint of standard angle bar and bolt for 30 lb. rail-1908 (Folder f023)
  - Louis Kaufman, Agt.-Sketch of angle bar-1909 (Folder f023)
  - Louis Kaufman, Agt.-Sketch of a 60# A.S.C.E. section Lackawanna angle bar-1909 (Folder f023)
  - Kilby Locomotive & Machine Works-Blueprint of angle bar for 56# rail-1906 (Box-folder 1230:24)
  - Kilby Locomotive & Machine Works-Sketch of a section of 53# rail-1906 (Box-folder 1230:24)
  - Kilby Locomotive & Machine Works-Sketch of an angle bar-1906 (Box-folder 1230:24)
  - MacArthur Brothers Co.- Blueprints of footstraps and bolts and bill for iron work for 100 ft. tail tower-1906 (Box-folder 1230:24)
  - Mankin Construction Co.-Schedule of iron and steel for warehouse for American Cigar Co.-1906 (Box-folder 1230:24)
  - The Macclesfield Co.-Sketch of iron lintels-1906 (Box-folder 1230:24)
  - Richmond, Fredericksburg & Potomac Railroad Co.- Blueprint showing method of fastening deck to steel stringers of trestles-1904 Nov. 2 (Box-folder 1230:24)
  - W.M. Ritter Lumber Co.-Blueprint of wheels for log loader-1906 (Box-folder 1230:24)
  - W.W. Robinson-Correspondence and drawing of wooden post-1906 (Box-folder 1230:24)
  - Rutland Railroad Co.-Blueprint of standard joint for Scranton 56 lb. rail-1904 Dec. (Box-folder 1230:24)
  - Edgar M. Smith-Blueprint of rail flange plate-1905 Feb. 24 (Box-folder 1230:25)
  - John C. Stout-Drawing of iron beams-1906 (Box-folder 1230:25)
  - Buffalo Foundry Co.-Pamphlet about the plant-1904 (Box-folder 1230:25)
  - Butters Lumber Co.-Drawing of small iron shive or pulley-1904 (Box-folder 1230:25)
  - American Locomotive Co.-Blueprint of a four wheel saddle tank engine-M.S. Sketch No. 2381-1910 (Box-folder 1230:25)
  - Armour Fertilizer Works-Blue print for 4 ton capacity acid egg-1910 (Box-folder 1230:25)
  - Tidewater Railway Co.-Blueprint of standard pile trestle-1906 (Box-folder 1230:25)
  - Tidewater Railway Co.-Blueprint of rods, bolts, and trusses and price list from Tredegar-1906 (Box-folder 1230:25)
  - Tidewater Railway Co.-Blueprint of standard frame trestle-1906 (Box-folder 1230:25)
  - George W. Tiller- Correspondence and bid proposals from Tredegar to Tiller- 1906 July 1, 1906 Aug. 15, 1906 Oct. 21 (Box-folder 1230:25)
  - A.M. Burroughs Lumber Co.- Drawing and specifications for two pair of Tender wheels on axles- 1908 (Box-folder 1230:26)
  - Hartfelder-Garbutt Co.-Sketch of fish plates-1909 (Box-folder 1230:26)
  - Hartford Steam Boiler-Correspondence regarding inspections of Tredegar steam boilers-1908-1909 (Box-folder 1230:26)
  - The Jos. Joseph & Bros. Co.- Blueprint plan of turntable lying dis-mantled at Woodbury, NJ, 1909 Apr. 15 and Blueprint of turntable at Bridgeton, NJ (Box-folder 1230:26)
  - Louis Kaufman, Agt.-Sketch of 34# plain joints for 75 pair angle bars and sketch of 45# rails for 50 pair angle bars -1909 (Box-folder 1230:26)
  - Louis Kaufman, Agt.-Sketch of plain joints for 3 3/4 lb. and 4 lb.-1909 (Box-folder 1230:26)
  - Greenleaf Johnson Lumber Co.-Sketch of 4 pair wheels on axles-1910 (Box-folder 1230:27)
  - Louis Kaufman, Agt.-Sketch of angle bar-1910 (Box-folder 1230:27)
  - Newhall Chain Forge and Iron Co.- Sketch #N 4235-2-18 of forgings-1909 (Box-folder 1230:27)
  - Plymouth Lumber Co.-Sketch of fish plates for 25 lb. rail-1911 (Box-folder 1230:27)
  - William Wharton Jr. & Co., Inc.-Blueprint of a tee rail-1909 (Box-folder 1230:27)
  - Richmond Pattern and Structural Iron Works-Tracing of columns and price quote from Tredegar-1908 (Box-folder 1230:27)
  - The Virginian Railway Co.-Blueprint for standard station details seat-1908 (Box-folder 1230:27)
  - United States Army-Frankford Arsenol (Phila., Pa.)-Specifications for shrapnel cases-1911 (Box-folder 1230:27)
  - U.S. Navy Disbursing Office-Vouchers to Tredegar Co. for reserve ammunition produced-1910-1911 (Box-folder 1230:27)
  - U.S. Army-War Dept.-General Depot-Quartermaster's Dept.-Jeffersonville, In.-Proposals for quartermaster's supplies required at Jefferson Depot-1911 (Box-folder 1230:27)
  - Kilby Locomotive & Machine Works-Two sketches of angle bars-1909 (Folder f028)
  - Kilby Locomotive & Machine Works-Sketch of angle bars-1909 (Folder f028)
  - Norfolk & Western Railway Co.- Blueprints of bridge no. 699 in Sheperdstown, W.Va. (Drawings no. 8066 and Y-6711), 1907-1908 (Folder f028)
  - Norfolk Southern Railroad Co.-Blueprint of standard 56 lb. rail joint and angle bar section #63 cat. 1905-1911 (Folder f028)
  - Atwood Paxson & Co.-Blueprint Sketch No. 2 and No. 3 of fish plates-1911 (Folder f028)
  - Roanoke Guano Co.-Blueprint of details of iron work for lump ore furnaces (No. 2207) and bill of iron work for 18 lump furnaces-1907 (Folder f028)
  - Richmond and Henrico Railway Co.-Blueprint of grate bar-1912 (Folder f028)
  - Virginia-Carolina Chemical Co.-Blueprint of inlet spout for mill elevator boot tank (No. 27710), 1911 (Folder f028)
  - M.H. Treadwell Co.-Blueprint no. P6355 of railroad coupler pins- 1909 (Box-folder 1230:29)
  - C.R. Johnson-Specification for iron straps for spar buoys with bolts to secure the same-1911 (Box-folder 1230:29)
  - Smith-Courtney Co.-Blueprint from Whiting Foundry Equipment Co. of standard worm geared reservoir ladle- No. 3052-1902 (Box-folder 1230:29)
  - American Steel & Wire Co.-Advertisement of triangle mesh concrete reinforcement from "Engineering Record", 1910 Dec. 31, Pg. 11 (Box-folder 1230:29)
  - Central Georgia Railway Co.-Blueprint of standard 70 lb. rail and angle bar for paved streets (No. 2450-1913) (Box-folder 1230:29)
  - Atlas Publishing Co.-Application to be listed in the Standard Iron-Steel-Metal Directory-1917 (Box-folder 1230:29)
  - J.E. Franks-Blueprint of a 60 lb. rail and angle bars-1918 (Box-folder 1230:29)
  - Baldwin Locomotive Works-Blueprint card of Tender truck wheels-1918 (Box-folder 1230:29)
  - Baugh Chemical Co.-Blueprint of acid egg, capacity 4 tons (No. 931-1917) (Box-folder 1230:29)
  - Birmingham Rail & Locomotive Co.-Blueprint of angle bars (No. 298-1917) (Box-folder 1230:29)
  - Kilby Locomotive and Machine Works- Blueprint of angle bars-1911 (Folder f030)
  - Carnegie Steel Co.- Blueprint of 3 inch field and 15 pdr. guns, cast iron shot-1903 (Folder f030)
  - North Fork Lumber Co.-Drawing of angle bar-1914 (Folder f030)
  - New York Switch & Crossing Co.-Sketch of angle bars, 22" long-1917 (Folder f030)
  - American International Shipbuilding Co.-Blueprint of a mushroom ventilator (No. H5370), 1917 (Folder f030)
  - Mobile & Ohio Railroad Co.-Blueprint of 60 lb. rail, angle bar, bolt, nut, and lock (No. A-8-Y-47), 1899 (Folder f030)
  - Baldwin Locomotive Works-Schedule of scrap material for sale-1917 (Folder f030)
  - Birmingham Rail & Locomotive Co.-Sketch of angle bars-1917 (Folder f030)
  - Mobile & Ohio Railroad Co.-Blueprint of standard track bolt- (No. A3X68 pg. 17), 1917 (Box-folder 1230:31)
  - Arbuckle Brothers-Blueprint for 80# ASCE rail-1918 (Box-folder 1230:31)
  - Birmingham Rail & Locomotive Co.-Blueprint of 56# rail angle bars for the Texas Co.-1918 (Box-folder 1230:31)
  - Gauley Mountain Coal Co.-Analyses and tests of coal and coke of Gauley Mountain coal-1919 (Box-folder 1230:31)
  - Georgia Colored Industrial and Orphans School-Report and annual rally-1917-1918 (Box-folder 1230:31)
  - Georgia Southern & Florida Railway Co.-Blueprint of rail (No. #1485) (Box-folder 1230:31)
  - R.C. Hoffman & Co.-Blueprint of splice bars-1919 (Box-folder 1230:31)
  - C.T. Patterson Co.-Blueprint plan of 56 lb. rail strap-1917 (Box-folder 1230:31)
  - C.T. Patterson Co.-Sketch of angle bars-1918 (Box-folder 1230:31)
  - Southern Iron & Equipment Co.-Blueprint of angle bars-1917 (Box-folder 1230:31)
  - Mobile & Ohio Railroad Co.-Blueprint of 60 lbs. rail, angle bar, bolt, nut, and lock (No. A8Y48), 1899 (Folder f032)
  - Kilby Frog & Switch Co.-Four sketches of angle bars-1919 (Folder f032)
  - C.T. Patterson Co.-Sketch of angle bar-1918 (Folder f032)
  - C.T. Patterson Co.-Sketch of angle bar for 61 1/2 # rail-1918 (Folder f032)
  - Southern Iron & Equipment Co.-Sketch of fish plates-1918 (Folder f032)
  - Standard Boiler & Plate Iron Co.-Blueprint of 18" truck wheel-(No. 769), 1918 (Box-folder 1230:33)
  - Treadwell Engineering Co.-Blueprint of boom mountings (No. 1077), 1918 (Box-folder 1230:33)
  - Virginia Iron Coal and Coke Co.-Blueprint of angle bar for 52# rail-1918 (Box-folder 1230:33)
  - Washington Steel & Ordnance Co.-Blueprint of copper band for 12" proof shot (No. I-S-1515), 1918 (Box-folder 1230:33)
  - American Iron Products Co.-Sketch of fish plates-1903 (Box-folder 1230:33)
  - Belmont Iron Works-Blueprint of cast iron idler wheels and double flanged chilled tread wheels-1919 (Box-folder 1230:33)
  - Georgia Southern & Florida Railroad-Blueprint of angle bars for 60# rail-1919 (Box-folder 1230:33)
  - Jameson, McKenzie & Evans-Correspondence and lists of types of steel reinforcing bars-1920 (Box-folder 1230:33)
  - Marion Steam Shovel Co.-Blueprint of 90 lbs. rail-1920 (Box-folder 1230:33)
  - Norfolk & Western Railroad-Blueprint of Christie brake shoe (No. B-5830), 1919 (Box-folder 1230:33)
  - Pittsburgh Rolls Corp.-Agreement-1919 Oct. 4 (Box-folder 1230:33)
  - Hartfelder-Garbutt Machinery Co.-Sketch of fish plate-1919 (Folder f034)
  - Stonega Coke and Coal Co.-Blueprint of low type mine car for Roda plant-1917 (Folder f034)
  - Sloss-Sheffield Steel & Iron Co.- Blueprint of a clevis for mine car (No. D-604) and blueprint of irons for flat top mine cars (No. E-347)-1920 (Folder f034)
  - Koppel Industrial Car and Equipment Co.-Blueprint of splice bars for 40# rail--1920 (Folder f034)
  - Pittsburgh Iron & Steel Foundries Co.-Blueprint of three pinions (No. 4425 and 460)-1920 (Folder f034)
  - S. Morgan Smith Co.-Blueprint of 14'-0" fly wheel-1919 (Folder f034)
  - Standard Scale and Supply Co.-Blueprint of building plan Class A (No. 231)-1920 (Folder f034)
  - Wheeling Mold & Foundry Co.-Blueprint of fly wheel (No. 9720)-1920 (Folder f034)
  - Wabash Railway Co.-Blueprint of steel underframe details for 5,000 to 6,999 coal cars (No. C895, C896)-1920 (Folder f034)
  - Seaboard Air Line Railroad-Blueprint drawing and specifications for standard track spikes-1915 (Box-folder 1230:35)
  - Southern Supply Co.-Sketch of two fish plates-1919 (Box-folder 1230:35)
  - St. Johns River Terminal Co.-Two blueprints of 60 lbs. rails (No. 1484 and 1488), 1912 (Box-folder 1230:35)
  - Seaboard Air Line Railroad Co.-Blueprint of winding shaft chain and connections (No. C2-1172), 1920 (Box-folder 1230:35)
  - James Stewart & Co., Inc.-Blueprint of cleats and bollards (No. 3270-A), 1918 (Box-folder 1230:35)
  - Taylor-Parker Company Inc.-Sketch of fish plates-1919 (Box-folder 1230:35)
  - Bethlehem Steel Co.-Blueprint of fly wheel by Tredegar-1920 (Box-folder 1230:35)
  - Brewer-Titchener Corp.-Blueprint of drop forged grab iron-1921 (Box-folder 1230:35)
  - J.R. Johnson & Co.-Blueprint of freight car axle with 5 1/2" x 10" journals (No. B-6325), 1920 (Box-folder 1230:35)
  - Kress Box Co.-Sketch of push car wheels and axles, 16" or 18" diameter-1920 (Box-folder 1230:35)
  - Penn Seaboard Steel Corp.-Blueprint of herringbone tooth mill pinion-1920 (Box-folder 1231:36)
  - Tredegar-Rolling Mill Dept.-Agreements-1920 (Box-folder 1231:36)
  - C.T. Patterson Co.-Sketch of angle bars-1920 (Box-folder 1231:36)
  - Standard Rail & Steel Co.-Blueprint of 75lb. angle bar, sec. 754B (No. B1203)-1920 (Box-folder 1231:36)
  - Woodward Iron Co.-Blueprint of angle bar to fit 90# rail section-1919 (Box-folder 1231:36)
  - Woodward Iron Co.-Sketche of special fish plate for no. 1 mine and sketch of angle bar for no. 1 mine dolomite-1920 (Box-folder 1231:36)
  - George D. Whitcomb Co.-Blueprint showing hauling capacities of various machines-1920 (Box-folder 1231:36)
  - Fairbanks Co.- Sketch of fishplates for section 42 for 25# rail (Box-folder 1231:36)
  - Central Supply Co.-Blueprint of standard mine car 1915 type-1917 (Folder f037)
  - Turner Supply Co.-Sketch of angle bars for 56 # rail-1921 (Folder f037)
  - The Connersville Blower Co.-Blueprint of 45 ft. special blower (No. A 1702)-1922 (Folder f037)
  - Virginian Railway Co.-Blueprint of truck brake levers (No. 224-C)-1918 (Folder f037)
  - Whiting Corp.-Blueprint of truck ladle (No. 7941)-1908 (Folder f037)
  - Birmingham Rail & Locomotive Co.-Sketch of angle bars-1923 (Folder f037)
  - Camp Manufacturing Co.-Sketch of angle bars-1923 (Folder f037)
  - S.W. Lindheimer- Blueprint of 56# rail section (No. 123-B) and 56# rail splice (No. 94-B)-1923 (Folder f037)
  - Newport News Shipbuilding and Dry Dock Co.-Blueprint of flashing street lamp base and column (No. 123484)-1923 (Folder f037)
  - R. Massie Nolting (for Chesapeake Iron Works)-Blueprint of sash weight floor & casting storage-1923 (Folder f037)
  - L.B. Foster Co.-Blueprint of standard 60 lb. rail and angle bar-1916 (Box-folder 1231:38)
  - W.W. Lindsay & Co.-Blueprint and specifications for cast iron manhole frames and covers (No. 5808-14) (Box-folder 1231:38)
  - Mobile & Ohio Railroad Co.-Blueprint for standard track bolt for 85 # rail and under (No. A-3-X-68 page 17)-1920 (Box-folder 1231:38)
  - Mobile & Ohio Railroad Co.-Blueprint for standard 60# Carnegie rail no. 60 K (No. A-3-X-68 page 75)-1919 (Box-folder 1231:38)
  - United Railway Supply Co.- Blueprint of angle bars-1921 (Box-folder 1231:38)
  - American Railway Device Co.-Blueprint of angle iron backings needed for mail chute in building (No. 1834)-1922 (Box-folder 1231:38)
  - Seaboard Air Line Railway Co.-Blueprint of fire hooks (No. 182)- 1903 (2 copies) (Box-folder 1231:38)
  - Seaboard Air Line Railway Co.-Blueprint of link-1916 (Box-folder 1231:38)
  - Virginian Railway Co.-Blueprint of standard track spike -1922 (Box-folder 1231:38)
  - H.C. Weller Co.-Blueprint of angle bar (No. 777)-1922 (Box-folder 1231:38)
  - Whiting Corp.-Blueprint of crane truck ladle (No. 3547)-1903 (Box-folder 1231:39)
  - Arthur Johnson- Specification and blueprint of base supported railway rail joint--1923 (Box-folder 1231:39)
  - Charleston & Western Carolina Railway Co.-Blueprint of standard 65 lb. rail and angle bar-1923 (Box-folder 1231:39)
  - Central of Georgia Railway Co.-Blueprint of standard 56 lb. rail and angle bar (No. 10635)-1917 (Box-folder 1231:39)
  - Charleston & Western Carolina Railway Co.-Blueprint of 70 lb. rail and angle bar (No. 3-C-25)-1915 (Box-folder 1231:39)
  - Charleston & Western Carolina Railway Co.-Blueprint of 80 lb. rail and angle bar (No. 3-C-23B)-1922 (Box-folder 1231:39)
  - Charleston & Western Carolina Railway Co.-Blueprint of 63.5 lb. rail (No. 18-B-22-A)-1924 (Box-folder 1231:39)
  - Newport News Shipbuilding and Dry Dock Co.-Blueprint of special post base for type x Milliken electric street lamp (No. D-2678) (Box-folder 1231:39)
  - J.F. Pennell Inc.-Blueprint of cast iron posts-1923 (Box-folder 1231:39)
  - Charles Ward Engineering Works- Blueprint of details of headgate track seat castings & screen track castings for Wilson Dam (No. 2393 A)- 1923 (Folder f040)
  - Louisville & Nashville Railroad Co.-Blueprint of standard 90 lb. rail, 53.3 lb., rail and 24" splice, tie plate and track bolt (No. E16169)-1924 (Folder f040)
  - J.W. Cain & Co.-Two blueprints from Gulf Coast Lines for 75 lb. angle bar and 85 lb. angle bar (Nos. 21-10 and 22-10)-1925 (Folder f040)
  - Gulf Coast Lines-Blueprint of 75 lb. ASCE rail drilling, angle bar, and track bolt (No. 21-10); blueprint of 65 lb. rail section and angle bar (No. 5); blueprint of 60 lb. rail and angle bar (No. 6); and blueprint of 60 lb. rail and angle bar (No. 7), 1912-1925 (Folder f040)
  - Louisville & Nashville Railroad Co.-Blueprint of standard 90 lb. rail, 53.3 lb. 24" splice, tie plate and track bolt (No. 16169)-1924 (Folder f040)
  - Standard Lumber Co.-Sketch of angle bars for 60# rail-1926 (Folder f040)
  - Sloss-Sheffield Steel & Iron Co.-Blueprint of skip car (No. 224)-1909 (Folder f040)
  - Panama Canal Purchasing Dept.-Blueprint from Isthmian Canal Commission of machinery for gatun and miraflores spillways misc. details (No. 8715) (Folder f040)
  - Smith-Courtney Co.-Blueprint of 24" high duty lathe (No. 40936)-1936 (Folder f040)
  - Southwark Foundry & Machine Co.-Blueprint of flanged wheels chilled cast iron (No. 152)-1923 (Box-folder 1231:41)
  - Virginian Railway Co.-Blueprints (2) for double seating for white waiting room in passenger station at Roanoke, Va. (No. A-1498)- 1923 (Box-folder 1231:41)
  - Whiting Foundry Equipment Co.-Blueprint for special casting details for #8 cupola for American Steel Co. of Cuba (No. 19141)-1923 (Box-folder 1231:41)
  - Atlanta and West Point Railroad Co.-Blueprint of standard track bolt with rolled threads (No. 102-B)-1922 (Box-folder 1231:41)
  - Bethlehem Steel Co.-Order Nos. 1428-F; 1066-H.S.; 1065 M.S.-1925 (Box-folder 1231:41)
  - William Cramp & Sons Ship and Engine Building Co.-Blueprint of cast iron wheel (No. P-6749)-1924 (Box-folder 1231:41)
  - Camp Manufacturing Co.-Sketch of angle bars for 40# rail-1925 (Box-folder 1231:41)
  - Eureka Lumber Co.-Sketch of fish plates-1924 (Box-folder 1231:41)
  - Eureka Lumber Co.-Sketch of fish plates-1925 (Box-folder 1231:41)
  - Eureka Lumber Co.-Sketch of fish plates-1926 (Box-folder 1231:41)
  - Eureka Lumber Co.-Sketch of fish plates-1926 (Box-folder 1231:41)
  - Richmond, Fredericksburg & Potomac Railroad Co.-Blueprint of arch bars for foreign cars (No. B-1503)-1923 (Folder f042)
  - Seaboard Air Line Railway Co.-Blueprint of ASCE rail joints (No. 4-1779)-1924 (Folder f042)
  - Shepard Electric Crane & Hoist Co.-Blueprint of upper and lower bearings for jib cranes (No. U-423)-1923 (Folder f042)
  - Suncrest Lumber Co.-Sketch of angle bars-1923 (Folder f042)
  - Southern Supply Co.-Sketches of angle bars (Section 3540 and 4040)-1924 (Folder f042)
  - Adams Co.-Circular entitled "A Vital Message to Foundry Owners" (No. 106-C)-1924 (Folder f042)
  - Donald P. Boyer-Blueprints for wheel pit cleaning equipment (No. 2220, 2222, and sketch of special separator for wheel pit cleaning)-1925 (Folder f042)
  - Carolina, Clinchfield & Ohio Railroad-Blueprint of standard 100 lb. rail A.R.A. Type B with Angle Bar Joint-1920 (Folder f042)
  - Camp Manufacturing Co.-Sketch of fish plates-1924 (Folder f042)
  - Chemical Construction Co.-Blueprint of cast iron work for Pacific Guano & Fertilizer Co. (No. 101-27-2)-1925 (Folder f042)
  - Crownshield Trading Co.-Blueprint of splice bars and bolts-1925 (Folder f042)
  - Empire Manufacturing Co.-Sketch of fish plates-1925 (Folder f043)
  - Empire Manufacturing Co.-Sketch of fish plates-1925 (Folder f043)
  - Empire Manufacturing Co.-Sketch of fish plates-1925 (Folder f043)
  - Norfolk and Western Railway Co.-Blueprint of standard track spike (No. L-311)-1920 (Folder f043)
  - Richmond, Fredericksburg & Potomac Railroad Co.-Blueprint of arch bars for foreign cars (No. B-1503)- 1922 (Folder f043)
  - Standard Supply & Hardware Co.-Sketches (3) of angle bars-1924 (Folder f043)
  - Standard Supply & Hardware Co.-Sketch of angle bar-1924 (Folder f043)
  - United Railway Supply Co.-Blueprint of standard rail joint for A.S.C.E. 80 lb. rail-1912 (Folder f043)
  - Virginia Iron, Coal and Coke Co.-Sketch of angle bars-1924 (Folder f043)
  - Tilghman Lumber Co., Inc.-Sketch of fish plates-1924 (Folder f043)
  - M.K. Frank-Blueprints (3) of angle bars for 80 lb., 60 lb., and 56 lb. angle bars-1924 (Box-folder 1231:44)
  - M.K. Frank-Blueprints (3) of angle bars for 90 lb. and 70 lb. rails-1925 (Box-folder 1231:44)
  - M.K. Frank-Blueprints (3) of angle bars for 56 lb., 60 lb., and 70 lb. rails-1924 (Box-folder 1231:44)
  - The Gregg Co. Ltd.-Blueprints (2) of chilled iron wheels (No. A-175 and A-176)-1925 (Box-folder 1231:44)
  - Hyman-Michaels Co.-Blueprints (2) of angle bars (No. B504 and B79)-1924 (Box-folder 1231:44)
  - Louisville & Nashville Railroad Co.-Blueprint of standard track spike (No. E314)-1897 (Box-folder 1231:44)
  - Louisville & Nashville Railroad Co.-Blueprint of standard track spike (No. E314)-1897 (Box-folder 1231:44)
  - Mill-Power Supply Co.-Blueprint showing end section of 60 # rail-1925 (Box-folder 1231:44)
  - Norfolk and Western Railway Co.-September scrap list-1924 (Box-folder 1231:44)
  - Steel Rail Supply Co.-Sketch of fish plates-1924 (Box-folder 1231:45)
  - Stroh Steel-Hardening Process Co.-Drawing of miter gear for mill drive (No. 9569)-1924 (Box-folder 1231:45)
  - Turner Supply Co.-Blueprint of angle bar for 80 lb. rail (No. D-2-29)-1925 (Box-folder 1231:45)
  - Atlanta & West Point Railway Co.-Blueprint of standard 80# rail (No. M.W. 1016)-1916 (Box-folder 1231:45)
  - Birmingham Rail & Locomotive Co.-Blueprint of 58 1/4 lb. rail (No. 511-15-F)-1925 (Box-folder 1231:45)
  - Camp Manufacturing Co.-Pattern for fish plates for 50# rail-1925 (Box-folder 1231:45)
  - Cameron & Barkley Co.-Sketch of fish plates-1925 (Box-folder 1231:45)
  - M.K. Frank-Sketch of 80# rail-1925 (Box-folder 1231:45)
  - Mobile and Ohio Rail road Co.-Blueprints for quenched bolts and angle bars (No. A-3-X-68 pg. 95), 1923, and standard 75 lb. rail section (No. A-3-X-68 pg. 84), 1921 (Box-folder 1231:45)
  - Western Maryland Railway Co.-Blueprint of standard 29" 100% angle bar for 90 lb. A.S.C.E. rail (No. 13-805-A2)-1925 (Box-folder 1231:45)
  - Camp Manufacturing Co.-Two sketches for fish plates-1925 (Folder f046)
  - Kilby Frog & Switch Co.-Blueprint for standard 24" 80 lb. ASCE angle bars (No. 980)-1925 (Folder f046)
  - Stewart & Roland-Blueprint of standard section of 25 lb. rail and splice bar (No. 1377)- 2 copies-1925 (Folder f046)
  - White Lake Lumber Co.-Three sketches of splice bars-1925 (Folder f046)
  - Albemarle Paper Manufacturing Co.-Blueprint for turbine shaft-1926 (Folder f046)
  - Clinchfield Railroad Co.-Blueprint of standard 100 lb rail with continuous joint (No. S-86)-1925 (Folder f046)
  - M.K. Frank- Sketch of angle bars-1926 (Folder f046)
  - International Nickel Co.-Blueprint of rolling mill plug (No. 12-51)-1927 (Folder f046)
  - James McGraw, Inc.-Sketch of fish plate for 60lb. rail-1927 (Folder f046)
  - J.W. Paxson Co.-Blueprint of equipment for cleaning car wheels-1926 (Folder f046)
  - Standard Lumber Co.-Sketch of angle bar with 4 1/2" punch, sketch of angle bar with 5" punch, and sketch of angle bar with 6" punch (Folder f046)
  - American Locomotive Co.-Blueprint of tender truck hub and tread wheels (No. 952 S 70080)-1926 (Box-folder 1231:47)
  - American Locomotive Co.-Blueprint of tender truck hub and tread wheels (No. 952 S 70080)-1926 (Box-folder 1231:47)
  - Baltimore Copper Smelting & Rolling Co.-Blueprint of crane trolley truck wheels (No. 1-E-222)-1926 (Box-folder 1231:47)
  - Camp Manufacturing Co.-Sketch of angle bars-1926 (Box-folder 1231:47)
  - Camp Manufacturing Co.-Sketch (2) of angle bar and fish plate-1926 (Box-folder 1231:47)
  - Camp Manufacturing Co.-Sketches (3) of angle bars and fish plates-1926 (Box-folder 1231:47)
  - Clinchfield Railroad Co.-Blueprint (2) of splice bars-1926 (Box-folder 1231:47)
  - Camp Manufacturing Co.-Sketch of fish plates-1926 (Box-folder 1231:47)
  - Frank Davies-Sketch of angle bars-1927 (Box-folder 1231:47)
  - Camp Manufacturing Co.-Sketch of angle bars-1925 (Box-folder 1231:48)
  - Camp Manufacturing Co.-Sketches (2) of angle bars and fish plates-1925 (Box-folder 1231:48)
  - Conway Lumber Co.-Sketch of fish plates-1925 (Box-folder 1231:48)